<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Freedom on Piero Macchioni</title>
    <link>https://macchioni.cc/tags/freedom/</link>
    <description></description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://macchioni.cc/tags/freedom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>La mia storia con internet</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2018-04-25-la-mia-storia-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2018-04-25-la-mia-storia-internet/</guid>
      <description>La mia storia con internet è cominciata da qualche parte negli Anni 90, in un internet cafè di Trastevere, a Roma. Eravamo in 6-8 compagni di scuola, davanti a un monitor 14’’, e non avevamo idea di che cosa scrivere nel box di ricerca. Ricordo che mi toccò l’onore della digitazione per due motivi: uno, avevo un computer in casa; due, perché qualche tempo prima, a casa dell’amico di un’amico “che ci capiva”, avevo visto comparire dopo una lunga attesa l’immagine di uno di quei manga un po’ porno che popolavano già gli scaffali della sua libreria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standing on the shoulders of tech giants</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2017-10-14-standing-on-the-shoulders-of-tech-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2017-10-14-standing-on-the-shoulders-of-tech-giants/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading a lot of good writing about Facebook, lately. Critics are fair and give us a lot to think about our relationship with the always on social network and the idea of &amp;ldquo;Building a global community&amp;rdquo;. As always, even before the Internet, it&amp;rsquo;s not enough we repeat &amp;ldquo;technology is neutral&amp;rdquo;. It is neutral, but we must commit so we get more good than bad, as Kevin Kelly said 7 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Save Net Neutrality</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/lets-save-net-neutrality/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/lets-save-net-neutrality/</guid>
      <description>Net neutrality is the principle that Internet providers should not control what we see and do online. The rules prohibit Internet providers from blocking, throttling, and paid prioritization—&#34;fast lanes&#34; - for sites that pay, and slow lanes for everyone else.
 Battle for the web
Let&amp;rsquo;s Save Net Neutrality</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>