<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Piero Macchioni</title>
    <link>https://macchioni.cc/tags/news/</link>
      <description></description>
      <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://macchioni.cc/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Standing on the shoulders of tech giants</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2017-10-14-standing-on-the-shoulders-of-tech-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2017-10-14-standing-on-the-shoulders-of-tech-giants/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://macchioni.cc/images/vault/southzuck.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;southzuck&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading a lot of good writing about Facebook, lately. Critics are fair and give us a lot to think about our relationship with the always on social network and the idea of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/notes/mark-zuckerberg/building-global-community/10154544292806634/&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Building a global community&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;. As always, even before the Internet, it&amp;rsquo;s not enough we repeat &amp;ldquo;technology is neutral&amp;rdquo;. It is neutral, but we must commit so we get &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2010/oct/24/my-bright-idea-kevin-kelly&#34;&gt;more good than bad&lt;/a&gt;, as Kevin Kelly said 7 years ago. But how can you work with something you do not own or comprehend? Because Facebook, as Max Read puts it in the first article you&amp;rsquo;ll read here, is «like a four-dimensional object: we catch slices of it when it passes through the three-dimensional world we recognize». So we need a four-dimensional approach, and a lot of patience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://nymag.com/selectall/2017/10/does-even-mark-zuckerberg-know-what-facebook-is.html&#34;&gt;Does Even Mark Zuckerberg Know What Facebook Is?&lt;/a&gt; by Max Read.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facebook’s actual value system seems less positive than recursive. Facebook is good because it creates community; community is good because it enables Facebook. The values of Facebook are Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2017/10/what-facebook-did/542502/&#34;&gt;What Facebook Did to American Democracy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The truth is that while many reporters knew some things that were going on on Facebook, no one knew everything what was going on on Facebook, not even Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nytimes.com/2017/10/12/technology/tech-giants-threats.html&#34;&gt;Tech Giants, Once Seen as Saviors, Are Now Viewed as Threats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their amount of concentrated authority resembles the divine right of kings, and is sparking a backlash that is still gathering force.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2017/10/13/opinion/sunday/Silicon-Valley-Is-Not-Your-Friend.html&#34;&gt;Silicon Valley Is Not Your Friend&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We need to break up these online monopolies because if a few people make the decisions about how we communicate, shop, learn the news, again, do we control our own society?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonus: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nytimes.com/2017/10/13/reader-center/social-media-guidelines.html&#34;&gt;The Times Issues Social Media Guidelines for the Newsroom&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The new electric spring of the News River</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2017-04-15-what-is-electric-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2017-04-15-what-is-electric-river/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://macchioni.cc/images/vault/electric-river.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;electric-river&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One week ago in Perugia, during the annual Journalism Festival, &lt;a href=&#34;https://scripting.com&#34;&gt;Dave Winer&lt;/a&gt; talked about journos taking back their online distribution system, now firmly in silos’ hands (blue silos, big F, you got it). He called that &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.festivaldelgiornalismo.com/programme/2017/plan-b-making-a-home-for-news-on-the-open-web&#34;&gt;Plan B&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First step, he said, forget your readers for a moment and start your own News River. It is something he’s been working on for years, basically a feed aggregator with no fancy stuff. It is radical because, when you use it, you just see what your sources publish when they do it: no algorithms, no distracting images, no ads. It’s like newsrooms in the old times, with the AP feed on your monitor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I’m simplifying but the old News River needed a server, a bit of programming and a few bucks to let everything run. Why bother if you have amazing free products like &lt;a href=&#34;https://feedly.com/&#34;&gt;Feedly&lt;/a&gt;? So now Dave shipped &lt;a href=&#34;https://rss2.io/electric/&#34;&gt;Electric River&lt;/a&gt;, a Mac app easily customizable - well, you can enjoy more if you know some coding - you can run on your desktop with no cost at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I’d be naive if I thought Electric River was that easy. I still think it has a steep learning curve for the average journalist (at least here in Italy).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically you have to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run a Mac.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know what rss feeds are.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to get them from your favorite sources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have some favorite sources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mix your sources so you don’t have too much information, aka too much noise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be happy with the super basic OPML editor Dave provided, or tweak your rivers building a few tabs (which I did)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be happy with no images, no embedded videos, no automagical hierarchy, no likes, comments, retweets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All considered I’m good with all the stuff above. But I’d really like some improvements to make Electric River not just a techie smart app but an app a journalist could use more at work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;actual-improvements&#34;&gt;ACTUAL IMPROVEMENTS&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;some kind of pagination: because if you’ve been away for a while, you lose too much news.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;search: I’d start with some &lt;code&gt;cmd + F&lt;/code&gt; for searching the page, but a search box would be amazing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;stars/readitlater: some kind of selecting items so you can work them later or just remember.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;synch: Electric River is totally desktop, but our lives are mobile and multi-device. Some kind of feed memory would help.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sharing: Dave offers his awesome &lt;a href=&#34;https://radio3.io/&#34;&gt;Radio3&lt;/a&gt; for tweeting and posting on Facebook. I’d love some more customization for sharing directly in Instapaper, Pinboard, Slack etc…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All of the above functions are already available from Feedly, Feedbin, etc…
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;ui-stuff&#34;&gt;UI STUFF&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’d really could use a “Return to Top” arrow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’d love to change the default font, text size, and background (like you can on Kindle or Instapaper).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is my feedback after one week. Electric River is only 0.40e, so it has still to grow.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>