<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data on Piero Macchioni</title>
    <link>https://macchioni.cc/tags/data/</link>
      <description></description>
      <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://macchioni.cc/tags/data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What would Jeff Jarvis do?</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2015-04-18-what-would-jeff-jarvis-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2015-04-18-what-would-jeff-jarvis-do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.howtostory.be/wp-content/uploads/2014/12/jeffjarvis.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;jeff-jarvis&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meno male che c’era la diretta live del Festival del giornalismo di Perugia. Insieme a un’altra ventina di soggetti connessi a youtube - perché solo 20, se ci sono 110 mila giornalisti solo in Italia? - ho seguito “&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.journalismfestival.com/programme/2015/keynote-speech-by-jeff-jarvis&#34;&gt;To hell with mass media&lt;/a&gt;”, la lezione di&lt;a href=&#34;https://buzzmachine.com/&#34;&gt;Jeff Jarvis&lt;/a&gt;, prendendo appunti come venivano. Li incollo qui sotto: bilingui, non corretti e disorganizzati. Poi magari, chissà quando, questa cosa diventa un post vero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;PS: la foto qui su viene da &lt;a href=&#34;https://stagliano.blogautore.repubblica.it/2015/04/17/jarvis-i-giornali-su-facebook-beh-forse/&#34;&gt;Riccardo Staglianò&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;individui, non masse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;se giornalismo è un servizio dobbiamo aiutare il pubblico a risolvere i suoi problemi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cambiare cultura e diventare un servizio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;####new relationships
- you have to specialize
- do what you do best and link to the rest
- public media: platform for media
- become community organizers
- old media is based on views and we moved it online: new metrics!
- no media centric, ma community centric
- membership? no another kind of subscription, but another way to collaborate&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;####new forms
- the article is not necessary the only form we&amp;rsquo;re gonna provide:
- tweet
- liveblog
- data
- &amp;hellip;
- we need to experiment
- be mobile ready
- &lt;a href=&#34;https://nyti.ms/1EVBUMq&#34;&gt;Zuckerberg&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;So what we’re doing with Creative Labs is basically unbundling the big blue app&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;google knows where I live and where I work, my paper does not&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;if we redesign news around community interests we get better value and provide best service&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;we&amp;rsquo;ve to reinvent tv news: con l&amp;rsquo;inviato che trasforma le notizie in uno sfondo per parlare davanti a una telecamera&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;oggi inserzionisti pagano per pubblicità che si vedono&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;if your goal is more clicks, you need more cats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;past from volume to value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paywalls?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://bit.ly/1HDn6D5&#34;&gt;What Could Google Do — for News?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;####Q&amp;amp;A
- rethink metrics: attention vs clicks?
- protection is no strategy for the future
- we need to experiment
- the metric that is going to matter is whether we are valuable in people&amp;rsquo;s lives
- we do not know what the internet is yet
- you don&amp;rsquo;t build communities, you just can help do something better
- reverse paywall: ti pago $20 e poi tu mi scali denaro ogni volta che twitto un pezzo, clicco su qualche adv, condivido una storia, ti do accesso a dei dati
- broadcasting is expensive because you need means for the masses? No, because you broadcast the old way&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>