<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Links on Piero Macchioni</title>
    <link>https://macchioni.in/categories/links/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Links on Piero Macchioni</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://macchioni.in/categories/links/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Butterball Hotline - June 2nd</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/2014/06/02/butterball-hotline-june-02nd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/2014/06/02/butterball-hotline-june-02nd/</guid>
      <description>###Links, tl;dr e idee altrui dei giorni scorsi
##NOODLES vs PASTRAMI A quanto pare siamo nell’Età d’oro del jewish-american deli food, ma io non posso fare a meno di essere tentato da questo libro che trovo citato ovunque: The Untold History of Ramen. _PS: quello qui su è David Chang di Momofuku._
##THE WHISTLE &amp;amp; THE BLOWER Edward Snowden intervistato dalla Nbc.
 What is right is not always the same as what is legal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butterball Hotline - May 12th</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/2014/05/12/butterball-hotline-may-12th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/2014/05/12/butterball-hotline-may-12th/</guid>
      <description>La coppia di popolari ricercatori non convenzionali, Steven D. Levitt e Stephen J. Dubner, sì, insomma i due di Freakonomics, tornano con un libro che esce oggi: Think Like a Freak: The Authors of Freakonomics Offer to Retrain Your Brain. Non sembra niente di che, sarà per questo che su Amazon lo trovate presentato da Malcolm Gladwell:
 Dubner and Levitt’s point, in their utterly captivating new book, is that following your curiosity—even to the most heretical and absurd end—makes the world a better place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butterball Hotline - May 6th</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/2014/05/06/butterball-hotline-may-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/2014/05/06/butterball-hotline-may-6/</guid>
      <description>Jack Bauer, 24: Live another Day.
 You know who I am. Trigger an alarm, and I&amp;rsquo;ll blow your head off.
 SPOILER ALERT. Walt Hickey su Fivethirtyeight ha calcolato, libri di Martin alla mano, quanto ci resta di Game of Thrones e chi avrà per protagonista.
 Let’s just say we’ll probably see tons of Kit Harington moving forward, if only because nobody has much left to do in the third book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butterball Hotline - May 1st</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/2014/05/01/butterball-hotline-may-1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/2014/05/01/butterball-hotline-may-1st/</guid>
      <description>L&amp;rsquo;evento con la &amp;ldquo;E&amp;rdquo; maiuscola: ICMC, l&amp;rsquo;Italian cycle messenger championship (Milano, 2-3-4 maggio).   Gilfoyle, That&amp;rsquo;s what the fuck I do (Silicon Valley, S01E02) &amp;gt;While you were busy minoring in gender studies and singing a capella at Sarah Lawrence, I was gaining root access to NSA servers. I was one click away from starting a second Iranian Revolution. I prevent cross-site scripting, I monitor for DDoS attacks, emergency database rollbacks and faulty transaction handlers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>