<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quotes on Piero Macchioni</title>
    <link>https://macchioni.cc/categories/quotes/</link>
    <description></description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://macchioni.cc/categories/quotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The psychological gravity of Facebook</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2018-03-27-facebook-psychological-gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2018-03-27-facebook-psychological-gravity/</guid>
      <description>This Cambridge Analytica scandal is generating a lot of interesting writing. I should bind that in somewhere. For now, let&amp;rsquo;s pin this.
 It is psychological gravity, not technical inertia, however, that is the greater force against the open web. Human beings are social animals and centralized social media like Twitter and Facebook provide a powerful sense of ambient humanity—the feeling that “others are here”—that is often missing when one writes on one’s own site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badass Stephen</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2018-03-14-badass-stephen-hawking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2018-03-14-badass-stephen-hawking/</guid>
      <description>Remember to look up at the stars and not down at your feet. Try to make sense of what you see and wonder about what makes the universe exist. Be curious. And however difficult life may seem, there is always something you can do and succeed at. It matters that you don’t just give up.
 Stephen Hawking, badass theoretical physicist, cosmologist and Big Bang Theory guest star.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Only Living Boy in New York</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2017-10-21-the-only-living-boy-in-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2017-10-21-the-only-living-boy-in-new-york/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s always mystery. You both know that. You both know it isn&amp;rsquo;t perfect. Excitement, trust and struggle, and the unknown privacies that keep us together. Glue of struggle. I raise my glass. The fragile glass we stomped on and shattered and will forever be putting back together, like the puzzles we first worked as children, learning to be patient, searching for what fits.
 -The Only Living Boy in New York, written by Allan Loeb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The light of day</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2016-07-13-the-light-of-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2016-07-13-the-light-of-day/</guid>
      <description> Maybe after wiping away the thick, grimy film of Facebook friend requests and Vine stars, we can all see the light of day.
  Mr Robot S02E01, eps2.0_unm4sk-pt1.tc  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The urges of eternal desire or temptation</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2016-05-15-the-urges-of-eternal-desire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/blog/2016-05-15-the-urges-of-eternal-desire/</guid>
      <description> «No matter in what city or what country I happen to find myself, the outside world I observe as I wander the streets presents me with the exciting, the mysterious or the erotic; my eyes roam freely over these sights and I release the shutter whenever I feel the urges of eternal desire or temptation»
  Daido Moriyama, Daido Tokyo  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>