<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Piero Macchioni</title>
    <link>https://macchioni.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Piero Macchioni</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://macchioni.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>archive</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/archive/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>open web</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/open-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/open-web/</guid>
      <description>In the last few years we&amp;rsquo;ve been seduced by the wonderful world of social media and social networks. They work beautifully. Unfortunately that means we&amp;rsquo;ve progressively lost control over our content and locked many of the web content into the social media walled gardens, accepting that our data may be used, bought and sold.
It&amp;rsquo;s a matter of privacy and a matter of freedom.
I believe, like the founding fathers of the World Wide Web, in a different kind of Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/about/</guid>
      <description>PM 2017</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact me</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/contatti/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/contatti/</guid>
      <description>You can contact me via email or via Twitter. I&#39;m also on Github and Instagram. At the moment I do not fancy Facebook that much (a few reasons here).  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Steven Pinker&#39;s Enlightenment Now can teach to journalism</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/2018-02-02-steven-pinker-enlightment-for-journalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/2018-02-02-steven-pinker-enlightment-for-journalism/</guid>
      <description>Steven Pinker&amp;rsquo;s latest fatigue, Enlightment Now, has already been tagged like the book everyone has to read - well - now. His big sponsor is a guy named Bill Gates and actually Pinker has a few bullets in his belt.
The book&amp;rsquo;s central idea is that we tend to forget the forces of progress the world has experienced, because our natural pessimism is reinforced every day by politics, media and viral false-beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeds for journalists</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/2018-01-17-feed-rss-for-journalists-copia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/2018-01-17-feed-rss-for-journalists-copia/</guid>
      <description>This year started with a small project I really like: Feeds for Journalists, by Dave Winer. The idea is that RSS is still a valid technology to get an effective and unbiased flow of news.
As he puts it, after reading a tweet by Mathew Ingram:
 If you&amp;rsquo;re a journalist and you love RSS, please join me in an easy project to improve both. Let&amp;rsquo;s put together a list of starter feeds for journalists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Only Living Boy in New York</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-10-21-the-only-living-boy-in-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-10-21-the-only-living-boy-in-new-york/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s always mystery. You both know that. You both know it isn&amp;rsquo;t perfect. Excitement, trust and struggle, and the unknown privacies that keep us together. Glue of struggle. I raise my glass. The fragile glass we stomped on and shattered and will forever be putting back together, like the puzzles we first worked as children, learning to be patient, searching for what fits.
 -The Only Living Boy in New York, written by Allan Loeb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A disconnected generation</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-10-15-harvey-weinstein-and--a-disconnected-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-10-15-harvey-weinstein-and--a-disconnected-generation/</guid>
      <description>We are constantly dazzled and blinded by power. We tend to allow and enable our leaders to play by a different set of moral rules and laws. While we distract ourselves with stupid selfies and pictures of our latest dinner, the real world around us spins out of control. Will we go down in history as the generation of connectivity that constantly disconnected itself from reality? I say - to hell with success and authority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standing on the shoulders of tech giants</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-10-14-standing-on-the-shoulders-of-tech-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-10-14-standing-on-the-shoulders-of-tech-giants/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading a lot of good writing about Facebook, lately. Critics are fair and give us a lot to think about our relationship with the always on social network and the idea of &amp;ldquo;Building a global community&amp;rdquo;. As always, even before the Internet, it&amp;rsquo;s not enough we repeat &amp;ldquo;technology is neutral&amp;rdquo;. It is neutral, but we must commit so we get more good than bad, as Kevin Kelly said 7 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good design is medium-agnostic</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-08-15-good-design-is-medium-agnostic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-08-15-good-design-is-medium-agnostic/</guid>
      <description>Good design is medium-agnostic ➡ @jasonsantamaria @offscreenmag
possed →  @leibniz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The best food review of the year</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-08-06-best-food-review-black-axe-mangal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-08-06-best-food-review-black-axe-mangal/</guid>
      <description>I believe this is the best food review I’ve read this year.
 Black Axe Mangal Lamb Offal Flatbread* There are dicks and vaginas on the floor. Metallica on the sound system, and the menu sometimes features something called a deepthroater. It’s so tempting to hate it. But then you eat former St John head chef Lee Tiernan’s dayglovibrant riffs on kebab-house fare, and you can’t help but acknowledge that you’re eating the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Save Net Neutrality</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/lets-save-net-neutrality/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/lets-save-net-neutrality/</guid>
      <description>Net neutrality is the principle that Internet providers should not control what we see and do online. The rules prohibit Internet providers from blocking, throttling, and paid prioritization—&#34;fast lanes&#34; - for sites that pay, and slow lanes for everyone else.
 Battle for the web
Let&amp;rsquo;s Save Net Neutrality</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The new electric spring of the News River</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-04-15-what-is-electric-river/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/2017-04-15-what-is-electric-river/</guid>
      <description>One week ago in Perugia, during the annual Journalism Festival, Dave Winer talked about journos taking back their online distribution system, now firmly in silos’ hands (blue silos, big F, you got it). He called that Plan B.
First step, he said, forget your readers for a moment and start your own News River. It is something he’s been working on for years, basically a feed aggregator with no fancy stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Un anno di &#39;Lo leggo dopo&#39;</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/2016-12-31-articoli-da-leggere-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/2016-12-31-articoli-da-leggere-2016/</guid>
      <description>Purtroppo anche quest&amp;rsquo;anno non sono riuscito a usare un solo sistema per salvare articoli e post in maniera organica. Ma come nel 2015 ho continuato a usare una ricetta di IF che permette di formattare in modo abbastanza decente tutto quello che salvo su Instapaper. Non è tutto-tutto quello che salvo allo scopo di una lettura successiva (vero Feedly? vero Pinboard?), ma lo sparpagliamento inorganico è parte della mia identità digitale, credo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senza Westworld non è vita</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.in/blog/2016-12-10-westworld-coscienza-illusione/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.in/blog/2016-12-10-westworld-coscienza-illusione/</guid>
      <description>Westworld è la serie tv HBO che fa parte di quella categoria dei serial che si guardano fino alla fine solo per capire che cosa tu stia effettivamente guardando. O anche di quelli che, leggendo la trama per la prima volta, dici: «Niente da fare, che è &amp;lsquo;sta boiata?». E poi chiedi scusa al dio delle serie tv.
Le prime 10 puntate le ho seguite così:
 Visione episodio. Lettura delle più assurde teorie sulla trama su Reddit, dove il popolo del web la sa veramente lunga.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>