<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mad Men on Piero Macchioni</title>
    <link>https://macchioni.cc/tags/mad-men/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mad Men on Piero Macchioni</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 16:02:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://macchioni.cc/tags/mad-men/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Butterball Hotline</title>
      <link>https://macchioni.cc/2012/02/22/butterball-hotline-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://macchioni.cc/2012/02/22/butterball-hotline-8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://moreintelligentlife.com/content/ideas/robert-lane-greene/which-best-language-learn&#34;&gt;Quale lingua conviene imparare&lt;/a&gt; (dopo l’inglese)? Se l’è chiesto &lt;em&gt;More Intelligent Life&lt;/em&gt; e la risposta non è il gettonassimo mandarino (che fatica a diventare lingua universale per colpa dei suoi caratteri), ma il francese. Prrr…&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;French is unquestionably top of the list. It can enhance your enjoyment of art, history, literature and food, while giving you an important tool in business and a useful one in diplomacy. It has native speakers in every region on earth. And lest we forget its heartland itself, France attracts more tourists than any other country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sono un fan degli &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gaspartorriero.it/category/Arduino/&#34;&gt;esperimenti di Gaspar&lt;/a&gt; con &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.arduino.cc/&#34;&gt;Arduino&lt;/a&gt;, mi chiedo solo che cosa potrebbe combinare se ordinasse anche un &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.raspberrypi.org/about&#34;&gt;Raspberry Pi&lt;/a&gt;, cioè il microcomputer da 25 dollari che può fare anche da media station HD.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Raspberry Pi is a credit-card sized computer that plugs into your TV and a keyboard. It’s a capable little PC which can be used for many of the things that your desktop PC does, like spreadsheets, word-processing and games. It also plays high-definition video. We want to see it being used by kids all over the world to learn programming..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Non per cadere nei soliti stereotipi da film di quarta categoria sulle mafie cinesi, ma &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.coverjunkie.com/blog/much-more/3/9037&#34;&gt;una cover così&lt;/a&gt; sugli &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.timeout.com.hk/feature-stories/features/48820/the-men-who-rule-hong-kong.html&#34;&gt;Uomini che comandano a Hong Kong&lt;/a&gt;, con tanto di artwork padrinesco, è una di quelle da mandare in tipografia dopo aver lasciato il Paese alla volta di una località segreta.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How did a small handful of tycoons come to rule over an entire city? Simple: They accumulated your wealth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Su &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wired.com/magazine/2012/01/pl_madmenmap/&#34;&gt;chi si è fatto chi e chi vorremmo che si facesse chi&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;Mad Men&lt;/em&gt;, che sta per ricominciare.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How did a small handful of tycoons come to rule over an entire city? Simple: They accumulated your wealth.
AMC’s Madison Avenue irregulars have done enough bed-hopping in 52 episodes to necessitate a diagram of the many entanglements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;«That was excellent. We should do that once a week!»&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4TcGEcKjSu4&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.ermetika.it/ermetika-resources/images/Image/immagini-struttura/key-play.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;play&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>